{
    "id": "5763f97d054748848e234480ac8ceba3",
    "title": "Gerunds Or Participles",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are …………………. too much these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "smoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03798f9f8b3e4039b5e547f464be9ebf"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a …………………… cigarette end in the ashtray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "smoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acf7b05b89bb45048f1813115e66777e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Having …………………  for ten hours, I felt great.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sleeping",
                "slept"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb9674a1845743e490ac091c7993d4ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not …………………… what to do, I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knowing",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "321489a3572a49fc9c21eccc57298929"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went ……………………… out of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90fe5044478d4d2facd07c83feb8d541"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… stamps is a hobby of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Collecting",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4aab68d858e34a1a80882bd3f4a70216"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate …………………. suitcases.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "packing",
                "packed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2651dc985a4a41c2901fae4df4bc2d0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry at Susie …………………… to lie to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "trying",
                "tried"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1db735ed53984133ae025d2bb927bbf5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The roof was ………………… off in the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blown",
                "blowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17fffdda3eef4456be43214aa6a31bff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested ………………….. a long holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taking",
                "taken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7d1fc186c6f4f328df4a93f5a74a6ab"
        }
    ]
}